<!DOCTYPE html>
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xml:lang="en" lang="en">
<head>
    <meta charset="utf-8"/>
    <meta name="description" content="Demonstrates some basic HTML content elements" />
    <meta name="keywords" content="HTML5, CSS, JavaScript" />
    <meta name="author" content="Anh Tran" />
    <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Lato|Open+Sans:100,300,400,700,900" rel="stylesheet" />
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://use.fontawesome.com/releases/v5.2.0/css/all.css" integrity="sha384-hWVjflwFxL6sNzntih27bfxkr27PmbbK/iSvJ+a4+0owXq79v+lsFkW54bOGbiDQ" crossorigin="anonymous"/>
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="styles/style.css"/>
    <title>Swap - Money Transfer | Index</title>
</head>
<body>
    <header class="header">
        <div class="header__logo-box">
            <img class="header__logo" src="images/logo.png" alt="Logo"/>
        </div>
        <nav>
            <ul>
                <li><a href="index.xml">Home</a> </li>
                <li><a href="product.xml">Products</a></li>
                <li><a href="enquire.xml">Enquire</a></li>
                <li><a href="Enhancements.xml">Enhancements</a></li>
                <li><a href="about.xml">About</a></li>
            </ul>
        </nav>
    </header>
    <!-- Finsih header -->
    <section>   
        <article class="article__top">
            <h1 class="article__top__heading-primary">
                <span class="heading-primary--main">Swap</span>
                <span class="heading-primary--sub">Cheap and Secure</span>
            </h1>
        </article>
        <article class="article__item">
            <div class="article__item__title u-margin-bottom-8">
                <h2 class="heading-secondary heading-border">
                    Why choose us
                </h2>
            </div>
            <div class="article__item__box">
                <div class="col-1-of-3">
                    <p class="u-text-center"><i class="fas fa-rocket fa-4x"></i></p>
                    <p>
                        Sign up, verify your account and get transacting. Recipient typically gets the money in 1-2 business days.
                    </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-1-of-3">
                    <p class="u-text-center"><i class="fas fa-chart-line fa-4x"></i></p>
                    <p>
                        We get you mid-market rates sourced directly from Reuters and add absolutely no margins! We charge a nominal fee.
                    </p>
                </div>
                <div class="col-1-of-3">
                    <p class="u-text-center"><i class="fas fa-lock fa-4x"></i></p>
                    <p>
                        Swap is brought to you by your bank or financial institution and backed by Australian Company, so you know that it’s super safe.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </article>
        <article class="article__item">
            <div class="article__item__title u-margin-bottom-8">
                <h2 class="heading-secondary heading-border">
                    Frequently Asked Questions
                </h2>
            </div>
            <div>
                <ul class="container">
                    <li>
                        <strong>What does Swap do?</strong> 
                        Swap is a leading digital cross border payments company which enables consumers, Small and Medium Enterprises and financial institutions to make international money transfers at a low cost. We were founded in 2014 in Singapore with licenses and offices in Singapore, Australia, Malaysia, Hong Kong, India, USA, Canada and EU.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <strong>Why use Swap over a bank or any other Money Transfer Operator (MTO)?</strong>
                        Transferring money overseas through banks and MTOs can be an expensive affair since they add unfair margins to FX rates and have hidden fees. Sometimes it's not even clear what the recipient's actually going to receive! At Swap, we are bringing transparency to the otherwise obscure world of international money transfers. We offer Zero-Margin FX rates, mid-market rates sourced directly from Reuters, and add no margin to it. We only charge a nominal fee to cover the cost of processing your transaction. We also maintain complete transparency and give you an accurate breakup of your transfer. In fact World Bank remittance site has consistently rated Swap as #1 cost-effective money transfer provider from Australia and Singapore to multiple countries.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <strong>How much fees does Swap charge?</strong>
                        Our fees differ from countries and corridors of transfers with typical fees varying between 0.25% to 1%. The fees are subject to change and can be reviewed for any given time on the Swap currency converter.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <strong>Can I open an Swap account for business?</strong>
                        Yes, you can. All you need to do is register as a corporate while signing up with us.
                    </li>
                    <li>                  
                        <strong>Is my money safe with Swap?</strong>
                        Swap is a licensed service provider with licenses in Australia, Singapore, Hong Kong, Malaysia, India, US, EU and Canada. Moreover we maintain complete transparency to give you better control over your transactions and our thorough verification processes ensure that your money is safe with us and reaches the right recipients.
                    </li>
                        <p class="acknowledged u-margin-bottom-8">Acknowledged content from: <a href="https://www.instarem.com/en-au/">Instarem</a></p>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </article>
        <!-- Finish section -->
    </section>
    <!-- Finish section -->
    <footer class="footer u-text-center">
        <p>
            <small><a href="mailto:tranmr@gmail.com">Mark up by: Anh Tran</a></small>
        </p>
        <p>
            <small><a href="https://www.swinburne.edu.au">&#169; Swinburne University of Technology</a></small>
        </p>
    </footer>
    <!-- Finsih footer -->
</body>
</html>